{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Torture_of_Silence",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance directed the film The Torture of Silence.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.886009693145752,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Torture of Silence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8075332641601562,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7661344408988953,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Abel Gance."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5443898439407349,
            "question": "Was Abel Gance a famous director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4700569808483124,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other films directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3983205258846283,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in Abel Gance's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3959423005580902,
            "question": "How influential was Abel Gance on the development of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3351932764053345,
            "question": "What genre might The Torture of Silence belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3271596133708954,
            "question": "What era was Abel Gance most active in as a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23220519721508026,
            "question": "Did Abel Gance win any awards for his filmmaking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance directed the film The Torture of Silence.",
            "html": "yago_4176_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era was Abel Gance most active in as a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_4176_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might The Torture of Silence belong to?",
            "html": "yago_4176_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How influential was Abel Gance on the development of film?",
            "html": "yago_4176_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_165.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4176_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Abel Gance directed the film \"The Torture of Silence\" (1917). This information can be found in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4176/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt and other files. Therefore, the triple \"Abel Gance directed the film The Torture of Silence\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this statement. For example, one document mentions \"The Torture of Silence (1917) was a Drama - Silent Films Film directed by Abel Gance,\" and another states that \"G\u00e9rard Bourgeois). In 1917 he played e.g. opposite Huguette Duflos in Madeleine (Jean Kemm), opposite Yvette Andr\u00e9yor in Un mariage de raison (L\u00e9once Perret, Louis Feuillade, 1916), and opposite Henry Krauss in Le destin est ma\u00eetre (Jacques Feyder, 1916). One of his first features was Abel Gance's Mater Dolorosa/ The Torture of Silence (Abel Gance, 1917).\" These statements confirm that Abel Gance directed the film \"The Torture of Silence.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}